Benjamin Miller

Seattle, WA – (206) 437-8494 benmiller92@gmail.com

Looking for Work

Capable, responsible student with experience in the videogame industry. I learn quickly and have the ability to think from both a creative and technical viewpoint. I work well with others and can take on the role of a project leader if called on to do so. I have the ability to learn how to make anything and to problem solve when things go wrong.

EDUCATION

McGill University - Montreal, PQ. Canada Cascadia College - Bothell, WA 2014 - Present

PREVIOUS WORK EXPERIENCE

Flowplay - Seattle, WA: Summer 2012, July 2013- Feb. 2014 Sound Engineer

- Debugged Sound Effects
- Created Audio Content for profitable web games

Temple Beth Am: Seattle, WA: 2007 - 2012

Teacher's Assistant

- Helped direct art projects for children
- Assisted office in providing class materials for teachers
- Learned team based organizational skills

Rathod Lab - Chemistry Department

University of Washington Seattle, WA Summer 2010, 2011

Chem Lab Intern

- Synthesize a special chemical compound used in the research on a cure for HIV and AIDs.
- Utilized a 20 step synthesis and helped purify and analyze the compound in order to get the specific molecular compound.
- Maintained purifying apparatuses and cleaned sensitive tools when necessary.
- Learned how to handle sensitive information and products in the context of work place safety.